I'm in Saudi Arabia right now and
there's cats everywhere.
And the government feeds them.
I'm in the port town of Jeddah, which is
the gateway for pilgrims going to Mecca.
It's an incredible place. I'm on a
layover right now, just walking around
the city,
loving it.
Tons of gold and perfume stores.
I bought a bunch of incense and it's got
tons of cats. They're literally these
cat feeding stations that the government
puts out to let the cats be happy and
well-fed.
In Islam, cats are mostly considered the
cleaner and more welcome of the cat-dog
debate. Helping cats is like a good
deed.
So, you got cats
everywhere,
which is one of the many reasons I love
walking around this city. I only have 9
hours before I have to fly out, but I
came into the city because the vibes are
so good.